{
  "questionnaires": [
    {
      "question": "A trigraph character begins with",
      "answers": [
        "#",
        "##",
        "?",
        "??"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the output of the following program? <p>#include&lt;iostream&gt;<br />\nusing namespace std;<br />\nclass abc {</p>\n\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; public:<br />\n&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; int i;</p>\n\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; abc(int i) {<br />\n&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; i = i;<br />\n&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; }<br />\n};</p>\n\n<p>main() {<br />\n&nbsp;&nbsp; abc m(5);<br />\n&nbsp; &nbsp;<br />\n&nbsp;&nbsp; cout&lt;&lt;m.i;<br />\n}</p>\n",
      "answers": [
        "5",
        "Garbage",
        "Error at the statement i=i;",
        "Compile error: ‘i’ declared twice."
      ],
      "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the storage specifier used to modify the member variable even though the class object is a constant object?",
      "answers": [
        "auto",
        "register",
        "static",
        "mutable"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "We can use this pointer in static member function of the class.",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Objects created using new operator are stored in __ memory.",
      "answers": [
        "Cache",
        "Heap",
        "Stack",
        "None of the above."
      ],
      "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "With respective to streams >> (operator) is called as",
      "answers": [
        "Insertion operator",
        "Extraction operator",
        "Right shift operator",
        "Left shift operator"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "i) Exception handling technically provides multi branching.\n\nii) Exception handling can be mimicked using ‘goto’ construct.",
      "answers": [
        "Only (i) is true",
        "Only (ii) is true",
        "Both (i) & (ii) are true",
        "Both (i) && (ii) are false"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the output of the following program? <p>#include&lt;iostream&gt;</p>\n\n<p>using namespace std;<br />\nvoid swap(int m, int n) {<br />\n&nbsp;&nbsp; int x = m;<br />\n&nbsp;&nbsp; m = n;<br />\n&nbsp;&nbsp; n = x;<br />\n}<br />\nmain() {<br />\n&nbsp;&nbsp; int x = 5, y = 3; &nbsp;<br />\n&nbsp;&nbsp; swap(x,y);<br />\n&nbsp;&nbsp; cout&lt;&lt;x&lt;&lt;&quot; &quot;&lt;&lt;y;<br />\n}</p>\n ",
      "answers": [
        "3 5",
        "5 3",
        "5 5",
        "Compile error"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the C++ compiler of Linux",
      "answers": [
        "cpp",
        "g++",
        "Borland",
        "vc++"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the built in library function to compare two strings?",
      "answers": [
        "string_cmp()",
        "strcmp()",
        "equals()",
        "str_compare()"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 1
    }
  ]
}
